[cheering]
["Hallelujah" playing]
♪ Now I've heard
There was a secret chord ♪
♪ That David played
And it pleased the Lord ♪
♪ But you don't really care
For music, do you? ♪
♪ It goes like this ♪
♪ The fourth, the fifth ♪
♪ The minor fall
The major lift ♪
♪ The baffled king
Composing Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Your faith was strong
But you needed proof ♪
♪ You saw her bathing
On the roof ♪
♪ Her beauty and the moonlight
Overthrew you ♪
♪ She tied you
To a kitchen chair ♪
♪ She broke your throne
And she cut your hair ♪
♪ And from your lips
She drew the Hallelujah ♪
♪  Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Now maybe there's
A God above ♪
♪ As for me, all I ever
Learned from love ♪
♪ Is how to shoot at someone ♪
♪ Who outdrew you ♪
♪ But it's not a crime
You hear tonight ♪
♪ And it's not some pilgrim who
Claims to have seen the light ♪
♪ it's a cold and it's
A very broken Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Oh, people
I've been here before ♪
♪ I know this room
And I've walked this floor ♪
♪ You see, I used to live alone
Before I knew you ♪
♪ And I've seen your flag
On the marble arch ♪
♪ But listen, love is not
Some kind of victory march ♪
♪ No, it's a cold and
It's a very lonely Hallelujah ♪
♪  Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ There was a time
You let me know ♪
♪ What's really going on
Below ♪
♪ But now you never
Show it to me, do you? ♪
♪ I remember when
I moved in you ♪
♪ And the Holy Dove
She was moving too ♪
♪ And every single breath that
We drew was Hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ I've done my best
I know it wasn't much ♪
♪ I couldn't feel
So I learned to touch ♪
♪ I've told the truth I didn't
Come here to London ♪
♪ Just to fool you ♪
[loud cheering]
♪ And even though
It all went wrong ♪
♪ I'll stand right here
Before the lord of song ♪
♪ With nothing
Nothing on my tongue ♪
♪ But hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
[crowd applauds and cheers]